[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fourth largest nation in the world in area?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Brazil", "USA", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie does this phrase come from: You are part of a Rebel Alliance, and a traitor, take her away!?", "correct_answer": "Star Wars", "incorrect_answers": ["Space", "Star Trek", "Space Invaders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Steven Spielbergs debut theatrical feature film?", "correct_answer": "The Sugarland Express", "incorrect_answers": ["Close Encounters of the Third Kind", "Duel", "Jaws"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the first town built by Europeans in the Western Hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "Isabella", "incorrect_answers": ["Porto Espana", "Santo Domingo", "Hispaniola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Grand Place, which is known for its large flower carpet, is the main square of this capital European city.", "correct_answer": "Brussels", "incorrect_answers": ["Berlin", "Paris", "Strasbourg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the version of King Kong that starred Fay Wray, Bruce Cabot and Steve Clemente come out?", "correct_answer": "1933", "incorrect_answers": ["2005", "1940", "1976"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many gigawatts are necessary to achieve time travel in the movie Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "1.21", "incorrect_answers": ["121.0", "100", "1.00"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to a sound caused by abnormal or pathological heart valves?", "correct_answer": "Murmur", "incorrect_answers": ["Aneurysm", "Wheezing", "Beat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin B10 helps to prevents early graying of the hair.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which Chinese river is the 2335 meters (7660 ft) long and 185 meters (616 ft) high Three Gorges Dam located?", "correct_answer": "The Yangtze", "incorrect_answers": ["The Huang He", "The Pearl River", "The Lian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Shish Kabob is very popular in this country. It is often served with the traditional greens and tomato salad, tahini sauce and pita bread.", "correct_answer": "Egypt", "incorrect_answers": ["Russia", "Germany", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The color coquelicot is a shade of this basic color.", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue", "Green", "Yellow"]}]